<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rakuten Mindfulness Network</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rakuten Mindfulness Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Core member interview: Alessandro Baffa</title>
      <link>/news/alessandro-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/alessandro-interview/</guid>
      <description>1. How did you first hear of “Mindfulness”? I first heard about Mindfulness some years ago on the social networks, following a French entrepreneur based in Silicon Valley, Loic Le Meur. He was talking a lot about it and how much this practice was spreading not only in the startups ecosystem, but also among a lot of very well known CEOs across the globe. I was so impressed when I discovered that there also are meditation sessions organized at the World Economic Forum, every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Rakuten Mindfulness Network is open for collaboration with academia, thought leaders and companies working in the field of mindfulness based corporate wellbeing. Especially we work with academia through a collaboration with RIT on topics such as understanding of mindfulness, organizational behavior and workplace wellbeing. If you are interested in these topics we like would to get to know you.
You can contact us by email here：rakuten-mindfulness@mail.rakuten.com
If you are interested in featuring our activities in news media please directly contact Rakuten Media Room (https://global.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming events       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media mentions</title>
      <link>/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are?</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Who We Are?   Rakuten Mindfulness Network (RMN) is an company supported employee-driven community established in July 2017 that aspires to uplift work and life of Rakutenians through mindfulness-based approaches . Employees who volunteer their time and talent to achieve this goal are the RMN Core Members. The Core Members are mindfulness practitioners who have benefited from their experiences of mindfulness practice. Their involvement with RMN is based on mindfulness, compassion, and joy to create a better workplace at Rakuten.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>